To build anything that truly lasts, it
takes time.
[Music]
[Applause]
The AP was slightly below the estimate
but grew by 12 and a half% on Y basis
whereas VNB and VNB margin below the
estimates. VNB margin was range bound at
25.1% on Y basis and the management
expecting the growth in H2 to outpace
the H1. However, for full FI26, the
growth is likely to come below the FI25
levels. The next is from the ICA Lombard
Insurance. The results were mixed. The
gross return premium were below the
estimates but grew by 2% on Y basis. But
whereas net earned premium were above
estimates and as well as the PAT the PAT
were uh above uh the estimates due to
the strong investment income but the
combined ratio lacked behind the
estimates. The management said for the
FI26 the growth to be led by the
commercial and retail health segments.
The next is from the Bajash s the has
accorded its approval for to both the a
for set insurance subsidiary for
transfer of equity shares held by
Aliance SE representing 26% of the paid
up capital to the company Bajage holding
and investments and the Jamal Suns
private limited. And the next is from
the uh news for the general stocks uh
insurance talks. The IDI approves the
norms for the rural social sector and
the motor third party obligation for F26
and F27.
>> Right. And Shahed what are the stocks on
your radar?
Supportive news coming in for Brigade
Enterprises as its flexible workspace
arm buzzworks has announced its latest
center at business park at high-tech
city Hyderabad spanning over 50,000
square ft. Up next is Adani Wilma's agri
business Q1 update. A strong update
coming in with the highest ever Q1
revenue coming in at roughly 17,159
cr rupees which is a jump of almost 21
odd%. The growth has been mainly driven
by the edible oil business which grew at
26% on a year-on-year basis. And the
management also stated that the raw
material prices have corrected by over
10% in the last three odd months. Also,
auto stocks would be in focus especially
in the EV segment such as TVS Motor
Bajage Auto as government sources to now
suggest that they are signing rare earth
related partnerships and now that has
become India's active FDA strategy. Now
India is in talks with signing
agreements with Chile, Peru and also
with Japan, Korea for rare earth
processing technologies.
>> Okay, thanks for that. And Von, lastly,
let's come to you. Give us a sense of
which stocks you think could be in the
spotlight today.
So let me start with Zidas life because
the company has received a final US FDA
approval for one of the
anti-inflammatory drug that is silic and
the annual sales in the United States
for this drug in the previous year was
around $122.6 million. So keep an eye on
Zidus life. Keep an eye on Dixent Techch
also because the company has you know
entered into a binding term sheet
agreement with Kungshan Q micro
electronics and its shareholder for the
acquisition of around 51% stake in QE
India and also the company has signed a
binding term sheet with Chongqing uh
precision manufacturing company that's a
Chinese company to form a joint venture
of around 71 to 21% ownership ratio and
the JV will focus on the manufacturing
of precision components of laptop,
mobile phones and automotives and also
other products. Also keep an eye on
Bioon because Bioon Biologics they have
expanded the diabetes portfolio with
USFDA approval for Kirsty which is the
first and only interchangeable
rapid action insulin aspart in the
United States and for Novalog the
overall sales in the United States was
around $1.2 2 billion for calendar year
2025. So keep an eye on Bioon as well
because this is a big update coming for
Bioon.
Okay, lots of stocks on our radar this
morning. But Janet, let's pick up on
HTFC live first. the fact that